export const Questions = {
    topic: 'Javascript',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What does CPU stand for in the context of computer hardware?',
        choices: [' Central Process Unit', 'Computer Processing Unit', 'Central Processing Unit', 'Core Processing Unit'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Central Processing Unit',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which programming language is known for its use in web development, both on the client-side and server-side?',
        choices: ['Java', 'Python', 'Ruby', 'JavaScript'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'JavaScript',
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?',
        choices: ['document.write()', 'console.log()', 'window.alert', 'All of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'All of the above',
      },
      {
        question: ' In object-oriented programming, what is the process by which a class can inherit the properties and behaviors of another class?',
        choices: ['Encapsulation', 'Polymorphism', 'Inheritance', 'Abstraction'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Inheritance',
      },
      {
        question: 'What does the acronym "URL" stand for in the context of web addresses?',
        choices: ['Universal Resource Locator', 'Uniform Resource Locator', 'Universal Routing Link', 'Uniform Routing Link'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Uniform Resource Locator',
      },
      {
        question: 'In the context of databases, which language is primarily used for querying and manipulating data?',
        choices: ['Java', 'C++', 'SQL', 'Python'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'SQL',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which programming language is often used for developing mobile applications for iOS devices (like iPhones and iPads)?',
        choices: ['C++', 'Ruby', 'Kotlin', 'Swift'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Swift',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which sorting algorithm has the best average and worst-case time complexity of O(n log n)?',
        choices: ['Bubble Sort', 'Insertion Sort', 'Quick Sort', 'Selection Sort'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Quick Sort',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which encryption algorithm is widely used for securing data transmission over the internet?',
        choices: ['RSA', 'AES', 'DES', 'SHA'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'AES',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which data structure stores elements in key-value pairs and offers fast retrieval of values based on keys?',
        choices: ['Array', 'Linked List', 'Stack', 'Hash Map'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Hash Map',
      }
    ],
  }